Captain Cat: Hehe... Gold! More gold! Hehe!
Cubby Bear secretly infiltrates the pirate ship in a strange bubble.
Cubby fights the pirate lookout on top of the ship.
Captain Cat: Watch the dame. I'll be back.
Crew Cat: Okay, Chief!
The crew member taunts the captive bear.
Cubby Bear kicks the crew member off the ship.
Cubby looks around the ship and finds his sweetheart.
Cubby Bear: Shh... I'm coming.
Girlfriend Bear: Ooo!
Captain Cat returns with a necklace for his captive.
Captain Cat flirts with the bear while showing off the necklace.
Cubby Bear secretly watches from nearby.
Cubby cuts the support beneath the captain.
Cubby Bear escapes to the top of the ship.
The pirate crew rushes after him and climbs toward the top.
Cubby Bear battles the pirates in a desperate fight.
```